Hari Sharma fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Special media records, 1970 - 2006; F-251-6; 47 moving images
  - Sound and moving images collection, 1980 - 2005; F-251-6-1; Physical description: includes 47 VHS videocassettes, 177 audio cassettes, 25 Hi8 videocassettes
    - Interviews of Hari Sharma, 1991-2005; F-251-6-1-0-8
      - SFU history: Interview by Amanda Camley, 1-2, 1999; F-251-6-1-0-8-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-4521)
      - SFU history: Interview by Amanda Camley, 3-4, 1999; F-251-6-1-0-8-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-4522)
      - Hari Sharma Radio Interviews: 1: Ambedkar, 2: Women, [ca 1999 - ca 2000]; F-251-6-1-0-8-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-4523)
      - Interview by Chris Nuttall-Smith (Vancouver Sun) regarding Ujjal Dosanjh, 2001; F-251-6-1-0-8-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-4524)
      - SFU History interview by Dino Rossi, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-8-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-4525)
      - Radio India - interview with Gurpreet; A day before Gujarat genocide forum, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-8-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-4540)
      - Coop Radio interview: Imtiaz; Second anniversary of Gujarat, 2004; F-251-6-1-0-8-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-4541)
      - CBC phone chat, CBC radio interview on Sonia Gandhi and prime ministership, & Radio Punjab interview, 2004; F-251-6-1-0-8-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-4542)
      - COOP radio interview by M. Briemberg on "The Final Solution", 2004; F-251-6-1-0-8-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-4543)
      - CBC radio interview over the phone about Air India case, 2005; F-251-6-1-0-8-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-4544)
      - SFU History interview by Dino Rossi, part 2, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-8-24 (Audio cassette OBJ-4545)
    - Audio recordings of South Asian community events and discussions, 1986-1999; F-251-6-1-0-9
      - IPANA public meetup, Philippines, Patayan and Pancho Lara, 1986; F-251-6-1-0-9-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4546)
      - Kothari - IPANA meeting, April 12/86, 1986; F-251-6-1-0-9-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4547)
      - R. Kothari - Ross St. Gurdwara, 1986; F-251-6-1-0-9-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4548)
      - R. Kothari, Surrey, Gurudwara, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4549)
      - R. Kothari, April 13/87; Media Centre - SFU sponsorship, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4450)
      - 22 July 87 Guest house / discussion with Cdr. Sen; Thai-Kampuchea border, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4551)
      - Discussion with Cdr. Sen II, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4552)
      - Refugee Camp site, then Army camp / Kampuchea - Thai border, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4553)
      - International conference on Kampuchea - Day 2, July 26/87, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4554)
      - Kampuchean Conference, July 26/87; tape IV, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-4555)
      - IPANA Public Meeting, Oct 18/97, tape 1, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-4556)
      - IPANA Public Meeting, Oct 18/97, tape 2, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-4557)
      - IPANA Public Meeting, Oct 18/97, tape 3, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-4558)
      - S. Shahabuddin, SFU, Oct 19/87, F-251-6-1-0-9-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-4559)
      - S. Shahabuddin, SFU, Oct 19/87, tape 2, F-251-6-1-0-9-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-4560)
      - S. Shahabuddin, SFU, Oct 19/87, tape 3, F-251-6-1-0-9-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-4561)
      - Syed Shahabuddin, IPANA Conference, Oct 17/87, Vancouver, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-4562)
      - Syed Shahabuddin, IPANA Conference, Oct 17/87, Vancouver, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-4563)
      - Shahabuddin: Resolutions, 1987; F-251-6-1-0-9-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-4564)
      - IPANA public meeting: Feb 12/89; Bonsor, chaired by Jyoti, 1989; F-251-6-1-0-9-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-4565)
      - William Hinton on Tiananmen Square & the Fugure of China; MR meeting, NY, 1989; F-251-6-1-0-9-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-4566)
      - IDEAS: The Maharajas, 1989; F-251-6-1-0-9-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-4567)
      - Santosh Rana, Feb 27/91, tape 1, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-9-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-4568)
      - Santosh Rana, Feb 27/91, tape 2, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-9-24 (Audio cassette OBJ-4569)
      - Santosh Rana, Feb 27/91, tape 3, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-9-25 (Audio cassette OBJ-4570)
      - Souren Bose, Feb 26/91, tape 1, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-9-26 (Audio cassette OBJ-4571)
      - Souren Bose, Feb 26/91, tape 2, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-9-27 (Audio cassette OBJ-4572)
      - Souren Bose, Feb 26/91, tape 3, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-9-28 (Audio cassette OBJ-4573)
      - CBC Ideas - India, Nov-Dec 92, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-9-29 (Audio cassette OBJ-4574)
      - Jyoti interview on sex toursim, COOP radio, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-9-30 (Audio cassette OBJ-4575)
      - M. Parenti on globalization, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-9-31 (Audio cassette OBJ-4576)
      - Shabana Azmi interview by M. Briemberg, COOP radio, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-9-32 (Audio cassette OBJ-4577)
      - Habib Tanvir on "Culture of Resistance", Douglas College, 1996; F-251-6-1-0-9-33 (Audio cassette OBJ-4578)
      - P. Sainath, NRISAD talk in Vancouver, 1997; F-251-6-1-0-9-34 (Audio cassette OBJ-4579)
      - Raymond Lotta speech: "No to APEC" at People's Conferece Against Imp. Globalization, 1997; F-251-6-1-0-9-35 (Audio cassette OBJ-4580)
      - Samanta (first public meeting), ca 1998; F-251-6-1-0-9-36 (Audio cassette OBJ-4581)
      - Adm. Ramdas' speech, Oct 24/99, NRISAD meeting, Douglas College, Surrey, 1999; F-251-6-1-0-9-37 (Audio cassette OBJ-4582)
    - Philippines research interviews, 1986; F-251-6-1-0-10
      - Peralta - Manila, 1986; F-251-6-1-0-10-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4583)
      - Entent - Manila (part 1), 1986; F-251-6-1-0-10-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4584)
      - Entent - Manila (part 2), 1986; F-251-6-1-0-10-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4585)
      - Interview with Dante, part 1, Manila, Sept 1986, F-251-6-1-0-10-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4586)
      - Interview with Dante, part 2, Manila, Sept 1986, F-251-6-1-0-10-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4587)
  - Photographic material, 1970 - 2006; F-251-6-2
    Hari Sharma was a self-taught photographer and frequently took a camera with him on his travels to India and other parts of the world. Series consists of contact sheets, negatives, slides, and prints depicting people, places, and events within his personal and professional life.
    Records have not been physically processed, arranged, or described beyond the series level. Further processing will be dependent on the archives' priorities and availability of resources in a future year.
    Photographic materials
    Access to photographic materials is restricted due to fragility and deterioration of the medium.
    Public access is restricted until the records have been physically preserved, processed, arranged and described.